Finding Aid for Stanford R. Ovshinsky papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Business Administration, 1943-2009
  - Institute for Amorphous Studies (IAS)
    - Lecture series
      - Recorded lectures
        - March 12, 1991--Hussain, Abid, "India and Its Energy Needs in the 1990s", U-matic videocassette (Box 102)
        - February 28, 1992--Fritzsche, Hellmut, "Science and Technology of Glasses", VHS videocassette (Box 102)
        - April 1, 1992--McNeill, William H., "Population and Modern History", 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 102)
        - January 19, 1996--Stempel, Robert C., "Personal Automotive Transportation: What is Ahead?", VHS videocassette (Box 102)
        - April 17, 1998--Stanford Ovshinsky: David Adler Memorial Lecture, video
        - March 22, 2002--Kastner, Marc A., "The Single Electron Transistor and What It Can Tell Us About Molecular Electronics", Betacam SP videocassette (Box 102)
        - June 14, 2002--Kirchheim, Reiner, "The Next Generation Materials by Microstructural Design", 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 102)
        - Boolchand, Punit, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 102)
        - Lucovsky, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 102)
        - Revez,Akos, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 102)
        - Shiff, E., (videocassettes also labeled Dr. E Suatux), undated; 2 U-matic videocassettes (Box 102)
        - Silver, Marvin, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 102)
        - Tauc, Jan, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 102)
      - Schedules, 1982-1986 (Box 59)
      - Speakers
        - October 25, 1984--Cooper, Leon (Box 59)
        - November 29, 1984--Twarog, Betty (Box 59)
        - December 6, 1984--Williamson, Samuel (Box 59)
        - January 3, 1985--Moss, Simon (Box 59)
        - January 17, 1985--Loferski, Joseph (Box 59)
        - February 20, 1985--Pankove, Jacques (Box 59)
        - February 28, 1985--Pohl, Herbert (Box 59)
        - March 6, 1985--Peave, Fran and Charlie Varon (Box 59)
        - March 21, 1985--Tsu, Raphael (Box 59)
        - April 9, 1985--Barna, P.B. (Box 59)
          (Lecture at Maple)
        - April 11, 1985--Greig, Dennis (Box 59)
        - April 19, 1985--Bennet, Jean (Box 59)
        - May 1, 1985--Schiff, Eric (Box 59)
        - May 15, 1985--Greenler, Robert (Box 59)
        - May 22, 1985--Schuler, Ivan (Box 59)
        - June 13, 1985--Leventhal, Marv (Box 59)
        - August 6, 1985--Spaepen, Frans (Box 59)
        - September 23, 1985--Wilson, Robert R. (Box 59)
        - October 10, 1985--Bachmann, Klaus (Box 59)
        - November 22, 1985--Hoffman, Roald (Box 59)
        - December 9, 1985--Hartman, Hy (Box 59)
        - January 6, 1986--Davis, Ted (Box 59)
        - January 17, 1986--Cronin, James (Box 59)
        - February 21, 1986--Frankel, Richard (Box 59)
        - March 6, 1986--Fitzpatrick, Nigel (Box 59)
        - March 7, 1986--Solomon, Peter R. (Box 59)
        - March 21, 1986--Schumaker, Bryan (Box 59)
        - April 21, 1986--Pauling, Linus (Box 59)
        - April 28, 1986--Mott, Sir Nevill (Box 59)
        - June 10, 1986--Edgerton, Harold "Doc" (Box 59)
        - June 20, 1986--Bell, James (Box 59)
        - July 7, 1986--Chidichimo, G. (Box 60)
        - August 1, 1986--Henke, Burton L. (Box 60)
        - September 3, 1986--Turnbull, David (Box 60)
        - October 8, 1986--Sze, Simon M. (Box 60)
        - October 29, 1986--Henisch, Heinz (Box 60)
        - November 19, 1986--Axelrod, Daniel (Box 60)
        - December 3, 1986--Carroll, Bob M.D (Box 60)
        - March 17, 1989--Adcock, Willis (Box 60)
        - November 19, 1990--Weisskopf, Victor (Box 60)
          (Contains a photograph)
        - March 12, 1991--Hussein, Abid (Box 60)
        - November 15, 1991--Salpeter, Edwin E. (Box 60)
        - February 28, 1992--Fritzsche, Hellmut (Box 60)
        - April 11, 1992--McNeill, William H. (Box 60)
        - January 19, 1996--Stempel, Robert C. (Box 60)
        - April 17, 1998--Ovshinsky, Stanford O. (Box 60)
          (David Adler Memorial lecture)
        - March 22, 2002--Kastner, Marc (Box 60)
        - June 14, 2002--Kirchheim, Reiner (Box 60)
        - March 16, 2005--Bienenstock, Arthur (Box 60)
          (Contains cd copy of lecture brochure)
    - Lectures, symposiums, and workshops, March 1984-Janufary, 1988 (Box 60)
    - Letter of commendation for Martin Steele, May 1985 (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous photograph negatives, undated (Box 60)
    - NATO Advanced Study Institute, August 1985-August 1986 (Box 60)
    - Newspaper clippings, August 1982-April 1987 (Box 60)
    - OvonicLink newsletter, June 1983-Fall, 1986 (Box 60)
    - Ovshinsky award nominations, January-May 1986 (Box 60)
    - Seminar, Summer, 1982 (Box 60)
    - Seminar, March 22, 1984; VHS videocassette (Box 94)
    - Seminar, March 23, 1984; VHS videocassette (Box 94)
    - Short course: Physics, chemistry, and applications of amorphous semiconductors, May 1984; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Symposiums and Festschrifts
      - Adler, David memorial symposium fund and obituary, May 1987-May 1989 (Box 60)
      - Fritzsche, Hellmut, February 1986-June 1987 (Box 60)
      - Henisch, Heinz, March-November 1987 (Box 60)
      - Mott, Nevill, January-February 1985 (Box 60)
    - Visitor register, March 2005-November 2010 (Box 60)
    - Workshops
      - Localized States in Tetrahedrally Bonded Amorphous Solids, June 18-20, 1986 (Box 60)
      - Photovoltaic, (2 folders of 3), August 24-25, 1985 (Box 60)
      - Photovoltaic, (folder 3 of 3), August 24-25, 1985 (Box 61)
    - Written works
      - Amorphous Semiconductor Handbook planning, 1983-1984 (Box 61)
      - Conferences
        - 1970--IEEE-Palo Alto (Box 61)
        - November 1984--International Photovoltaic Science and Engineering (Box 61)
        - December 18, 1984--Nobel Laureate Symposium (Box 61)
        - 1985--Society of Vacuum Coaters (Box 61)
        - April 1985--San Francisco (Box 61)
        - May 1985--China (Box 61)
        - 1985-- June (Box 61)
        - October 25, 1985--IEEE Photovoltaic Specialists (Box 61)
        - November 1985--Copenhagen (Box 61)
        - January 1986--SPIE-Los Angeles (Box 61)
        - March 1986--Macro-engineering, Washington D.C. (Box 61)
        - August 1986--AIChE, Boston (Box 61)
        - --Hungary, September 15-20, 1986 (Box 61)
        - --SPIE-Cambridge, Massachusetts, September 18-19, 1986 (Box 61)
        - October 1986--International New Materials-Osaka (Box 61)
        - October 1986--European Photovoltaic Solar Energy-Spain (Box 61)
        - 1986--SPIE-New Delhi (Box 61)
      - Cosmology paper, July 8, 1985 (Box 61)
      - Oped
        - "Is There an Evolutionary Brain? The Physiology of Politics,", January 1986 (Box 61)
        - "What is Realism?", August 3, 1986 (Box 61)
        - "U.S. and European Companies are Often Victims of Their Own Hubris,", November 1985 (Box 61)
      - Papers by the ECD group, September 1985-1986 (Box 61)
      - SRO miscellaneous, September 1984-March 1986 (Box 61)
- Talks and Recognition
  The Talks and Recognition series (16.8 linear feet, 2 oversize boxes, and digital files; 1959-2011) includes mostly correspondence, Microsoft PowerPoint presentations, speech notes, and certificates from Stanford Ovshinsky's awards. Ovshinsky served as a keynote or invited speaker at a large number of college graduations and scientific conferences around the world, so this series contains many of these speeches and speech notes. He did not limit himself to the high-profile stages of higher education and international scientific conferences, however: the series also includes notes documenting his visits to elementary and middle school classrooms. Materials from interviews given to media outlets ranging from local to international also appear, and rounding out this component of the series are presentations to shareholders and potential corporate partners. Included as well are details about awards that Ovshinsky received, ranging from numerous honorary university degrees and professional organization recognition to commendations of the ingenuity of his products and celebrations of his involvement in service groups.
  - Speeches and Talks
    - (materials with gaps), 1959-1979 (Box 107)
    - 1967-1980, 83 folders (Box 62)
    - "Applications of Amorphous Semiconductors for Solar Energy Conversion," January 1980/Ovshinsky, June 12, 1980/Energy Countdown, VHS videocassette (Box 88)
    - Supplemental lectures and talks, 1980; 2 folders (Box 107)
    - 1981-1985, 51 folders (Box 63)
      ( May 26, 1983 -- AAAS Youth Symposium-photographs)
    - S.R. Ovshinsky, "New Technology and Peace," Birmingham Unitarian Church, January 13, 1985; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
    - Ovshinsky at Grosse Pointe South High School Science Assembly, April 25, 1985; VHS videocassette (Box 94)
    - 1985-1988, 46 folders (Box 64)
    - 1988-1990, 41 folders (Box 65)
    - Japanese Society of Detroit, June 6, 1988; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
    - Ovshinsky, "Harnessing the Sun: New Technologies" at Fairfield University, October 11, 1988; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
    - "Harnessing the Sun" talk announcement poster, October 11, 1988 (Box 112)
    - 1990-1997, 46 folders (Box 66)
    - SRO, Civic Forum, Akron, Ohio, January 21, 1992; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
    - S.R. Ovshinsky, "How Can the Developing Countries Achieve Equality Through Alternative Energy," U.C. Berkeley, April 16, 1992; VHS videocassette (Box 95)
    - S.R. Ovshinsky, Lawrence Technological University, May 4, 1992; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
    - Stanford Ovshinsky, "A Nickel Hydride Battery for Electric Vehicles," MIT-EECS Colloquium, November 22, 1993; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
    - 1997-2002, 35 folders (Box 67)
    - 2002-2003, 22 folders (Box 68)
      ( October 15, 2002-EMCW Conference -- CD of papers from 1979-2002 sessions of the conference; March 6, 2003 -- SRO's Talk Hydrogen Conference -- CD of Proceedings and CD of Ovshinsky's presentation; March 10-11, 2003 -- EPCOS -- photographs and a CD; May 9, 2003 -- SRO seminar at Kettering -- CD Ovshinsky's presentation; August 22, 2003--Hydrogen Prius event at Uni-Solar--text of Ovshinsky's talk; October 1-3, 2003 -- SRO Keynote at Colorado School of Engineering Conference -- CD presentation; October 27, 2003 -- Newcastle University -- CD presentation; MRS Fall 2003 -- Tutorial -- CD of tutorial slides, Ted Nara Japan, and MRS photos; November 4, 2003--International Symposium on Optical Memory in Nara, Japan--text of Ovshinsky's keynote speech)
    - Stan Ovshinsky Japan Presentation Rough Cut, October 23, 2003; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
    - 2004-2005, 23 folders (Box 69)
      ( April 22, 2004-SRO at Temple University -- CD presentation; June 2, 2004 -- SRO talk at WSU AET Conf -- CD presentation;September 21, 2004 -- Walker Cisler Memorial Lecture -- CD photograph; October 19, 2004-Solar Power -- 2 CDs proceedings and presentation; November 8-12, 2004 -- Mexico Congress on Renewable Energy; November 8-12, 2004-- Intl. Non-Oxide Glass Symposium -- CD presentation; January 11, 2005-Colloquium of Michigan Center For Theoretical Physics -- CD presentation; Feb 17,2005 -- Akron Roundtable)
    - Science Lecture for Young People at Detroit Country Day School, May 18, 2004; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
    - Prerecorded EPCOS 2004 greeting, August 17, 2004, video
    - Photographs from Walker Cisler Memorial Lecture, September 21, 2004, .ZIP file
    - Mexico Congress on Renewable Energy presentation, November 2, 2004; video
    - "Akron Roundtable" on WKSU 89.7FM with Stanford Ovshinsky, February 17, 2005; .ZIP file
    - 2005, 16 folders (Box 70)
      ( February 26, 2005 -- SRO at Quarterly Meeting of California Hydrogen Business Council -- CD PowerPoint presentation; April 3, 2005-- Swarthmore College-CD; April 12, 2005 -- Meeting with ECD board -- CD presentation; April 16, 2005 -- Annual NYU Entrepreneurship Conerence -- 2CDs proceedings and presentation; July 13-15, 2005 -- intl. Hydrogen Energy Congress & Exhibition -- 2CDs presentation and recording; September 3-6, 2005 -- EPCOS -- Photographs and CD presentation; September 21, 2005-Renewables Conference -- 2CDs Rwanda Solar and presentation + video; September 28, 2005-Global Market Trends Conference -- CD presentation; November 30, 2005-MI COEJL Fall Gathering -- CD presentation)
    - NASDAQ Closing Bell Ceremony, March 30, 2005; video
    - Prerecorded presentation for IHEC Turkey, July 11, 2005; video
    - 2006-2007, 27 folders (Box 71)
      ( April 27, 2006 -- SRO at ACCESS -- CD presentation; May 4, 2006 -- Colloquium in Honor of 80th birthday for Prof. Bower-CD; June 7, 2006-SRO keynote at EMU spring lecture series-CD presentation; November 17, 2006-panelist at Technology Transfer -- CD; March 31, 2007-keynote at Illinois Institute of Technology -- CD)
    - "Civic Forum of the Air" talk on alternative energy by Stanford Ovshinsky, April 28, 2006; VHS videocassette (Box 88)
    - Prerecorded presentation for Boer Symposium in Germany, May 5, 2006; video
      (recorded April 18, 2006)
    - 2007-2009, 16 folders (Box 72)
      ( February 27-29, 2008 -- 1st International PV Power Generation Expo-DVD of talk; April 8, 2008-Berkeley -- Photographs and 3 CDs; September 29, 2008 -- U.S. Mexico Workshop-Photograph book; October 2-3, 2008-Keynote at nanoTX USA-CD)
    - Photographs relating to Berkeley presentation, April 8, 2008
    - Announcement poster, April 8, 2008 (Box 112)
    - 2009-2012, 19 folders (Box 73)
    - Presentation at the Ecology Center Annual Meeting in Ann Arbor, May 10, 2011; video
    - Presentation at the City Club of Cleve, September 23, 2011; video
  - Interviews
    - 1973-2011, 16 folders (Box 74)
      (2010-2011-Miscellaneous -- unedited video; November 2010 & May 2011 -- Radio WUPH)
    - Iris Ovshinsky, tape #23, undated; audiocassette (Box 89)
    - Stan Ovshinsky, PM Magazine on WJBK TV2, June 12, 1980; U-matic videocassette (Box 94)
    - Stan Ovshinsky and Nancy Bacon, Dow Jones Investor Network, June 29, 1995; VHS videocassette (Box 105)
    - "Energy Conversion Devices, Inc.," The International Corporate Forum, Dow Jones Investor Network, March 28, 1996; VHS videocassette (Box 95)
    - Stan Ovshinsky, August 2, 2002; audiocassette (Box 89)
    - Stan Ovshinsky interview, (name given on tape as Oshinski), August 17, 2004; audiocassette (Box 89)
    - Stanford Ovshinsky, undated; audiocassette (Box 89)
    - Stanford Ovshinsky, (name given on tape as Oshinski), undated; audiocassettes (Box 89)
    - Stanford Ovshinsky, ECD interview, undated; audiocassette (Box 89)
    - Stanford Ovshinsky/Ovonics, undated; audiocassette (Box 89)
    - "Nova: Japan's American Genius," PBS, October 27, 1987; video
    - Interview and profile on "City for Youth" on WTVS/WXYZ Detroit,", January 24, 1994; video
    - Interview on "Anything is Possible" with Jack Krasula on WJR-AM 760, (audio), July 1, 2007; .ZIP file
    - Interview for "Electric and Hybrid Cars: A Tragic and Unnecessary Loss for the U.S,", May 4, 2009; video
  - Recognition
    - Awards, 1968-2004; 47 folders (Box 75)
      (1968-Diesel Gold Medal -- Photograph and German;July 1996 -- Crain's Michigan's Top 10 Superstocks -- Photograph; 2000-Heroes of Chemistry-Photographs)
    - Coors American Ingenuity Award, 1988; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
    - Corporate Leadership Awards (Wayne State University), Thursday, June 21, 2001; VHS videocassette (Box 105)
    - Heroes of Chemistry, August 20, 2000; VHS videocassette (Box 105)
    - Awards, 2005-2011; 21 folders (Box 76)
      ( November 14-15, 2005-Economist Innovation Award-Sketch from front cover; March 17, 2009-Awards receptions at APS-Photographs)
    - Awards, 2012; 22 folders (Box 77)
      (European Inventor Award -- Nomination folder 1 -- Photographs and CD; European Inventor Award -- Nomination folder 2-Photographs)
    - Festschrift for Stan Ovshinsky, 3 folders (Box 77)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1980-2010
      ( May 2010 -- University of Michigan -- Photographs include Ovshinsky with President Obama)
      - Introduction to Stanford Ovshinsky played at New York Institute of Technology Commencement, May 18, 2008; video
    - Miscellaneous diplomas and awards, 1984-1990; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Oversize awards, 1988-1999 (Box 113)
      (New York Institute of Technology -- Leadership and Sustainable Technology award; Karl Boer Solar Energy Award; photograph accepting an award)
    - State government commendations, 1988-2006 (Box 113)
      (Honorary Citation from the State of Colorado; special recognition from Ohio House of Representatives on factory groundbreaking, )
    - Workmen's Circle: Stan and Iris Ovshinsky video tribute, VHS videocassettes (Box 102)
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Materials series (10 linear feet and digital files; 1947-2008) consists primarily of printed photographs, and digital images. The photographs depict ECD buildings, employees, and parties. There are also pictures of trips Ovshynski took to places like Mexico and Japan, in addition to publicity photographs of Stan and Iris Ovshinsky, and Robert Stempel. Other photographs of note are those documenting the visits of prominent individuals to ECD and Ovshinsky's 70th and 80th birthday parties. Ovshinsky sketched a great deal, and a sample of his drawings and doodles can also be found in this series. A few videos, largely produced by son Harvey's HKO Media, supplement the visual materials in this series.
  - Awards, undated (Box 78)
  - Board members annual meeting, December 19, 1995 (Box 78)
  - Companies
    - ECD
      - Annual report, 1973 (Box 78)
      - Drafting department, undated (Box 78)
      - Electrochemistry division, undated (Box 78)
      - Family summer outing, August 5, 2001
      - General structures lab, undated (Box 78)
        (with John Tyler)
      - Historic moments, undated (Box 78)
      - Holiday party at DIA, 1985-1986 (Box 78)
      - Honda signing, 1996 (Box 78)
      - Interior and exterior, September 1965 (Box 78)
      - Machine shops, 1984(?) (Box 78)
      - Open house, August 1981 (Box 78)
      - Original building, undated (Box 78)
      - Patent department, undated (Box 78)
      - Plant 1
        - Headquarters and development facilities, 1982 (Box 78)
        - Photovoltaics lab, undated (Box 78)
          (with Czubatyj)
      - Plant 2 -- Ovonic photovoltaic pilot plant, undated (Box 78)
      - Plant 3 -- Advanced materials lab and model shop -- Lake Angelus Observatory Conference and Seminar Center, undated (Box 78)
      - Plant 4 -- Hyrdorgen -- Electrochemsitry Development Facility, undated (Box 78)
        (Barrett Street)
      - Plant 5 -- Wet Chemistry Photovoltaic Etching, 1981 (Box 78)
        (Edwards Street)
      - Plant 7, undated (Box 78)
        (Heide Street)
      - Plant 8, undated (Box 78)
        (Premier Street)
      - Plant 10 -- Ovonic Battery Company production facility, 1985-1988 (Box 78)
      - Plant 11
        - Sovonics, July 1984(?) (Box 78)
        - Coating Division facility, 1984 (Box 78)
        - Dedication, undated (Box 78)
      - Plant 12 -- Legal, undated (Box 78)
      - Plant 14 -- Ovonic Synthetic Materials Company, December 1986 (Box 78)
      - Plant Japan -- Thermovonics
        - Undated (Box 78)
        - 1985 (Box 78)
      - Plant New Jersey, undated (Box 78)
      - Plant New Jersey open house, 1981 (Box 87)
      - President's Letter, 1995 (Box 78)
      - Support facilities, undated (Box 78)
    - Erricson Telephone signing, 1963 (Box 78)
      (Sweden)
    - EV Global signing, undated (Box 78)
    - Fuji Film signing, 1970s (Box 78)
    - GM Ovonic, undated (Box 78)
    - Hupp Motor Company -- Electric power steering, undated (Box 78)
    - Hupp Motor Company, Stanford Roberts, New Britain, 1947-1950 (Box 78)
    - Logos, undated (Box 79)
    - Logo animation, VHS videocassette (Box 79)
    - Ovitron, undated (Box 79)
    - Ovonic Battery Company
      - GM signing, 1994 (Box 79)
      - Tour de Sol, 1995-1996 (Box 79)
    - Ovonic Display Systems -- production facility, undated (Box 79)
    - Ovonic Memories Inc. -- Stan Ovshinsky, Al Adomines, and Jack Evans, undated (Box 79)
    - Ovonic Solar, undated (Box 79)
    - Ovonic Thermoelectric Company, November 1983 (Box 79)
    - Personnel with equipment, undated (Box 79)
    - Sharp-ECD Solar, Inc.
      - January-February 1983 (Box 79)
        (Japan)
      - Signing original agreement, undated (Box 79)
    - Sovlux Battery, undated (Box 79)
    - Sovlux plant, 1991(?) (Box 79)
    - Sovonics
      - Plant, 1988 (Box 79)
      - Plant dedication (Box 79)
      - n, May 31, 1984 (Box 79)
      - Town hall meeting, undated (Box 79)
      - Underhill signing, July 1986 (Box 79)
      - USSC plant, undated (Box 79)
    - Stanford Roberts Manufacturing Co. -- New Britain machine, 1949-1954(?); 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Suryovoics, February 1990(?) (Box 79)
      (India)
    - Texaco-Ovonic Fuel Cell Company
      - Undated (Box 79)
      - Groundbreaking and Cobasys grand opening, 2002; 2005 (Box 79)
    - Tour for Summer employees, 1985 (Box 79)
    - Uni-Solar
      - Greenville, undated (Box 79)
      - Mexico, undated (Box 79)
    - Visitors (Box 80)
      - British House of Commons delegation, 1981 (Box 80)
      - Carr, Ray, March 6, 1995 (Box 80)
      - Department of Energy, January 1985 (Box 80)
        (ECD and Sovonics Solar)
      - Japanese sunshine study group, March 1984 (Box 80)
      - Mott, Sir Nevill, March 1978 (Box 80)
      - Secretary of Energy -- Spence Abraham, August 2002; 2 folders (Box 80)
      - Secretary of Energy -- Bodman visits solar plant, undated (Box 80)
      - Senator Simon, March 6, 1995 (Box 80)
      - Shanghai Ceramics Institute, May 1984 (Box 80)
      - Teller, E., October 8, 1984 (Box 80)
      - Young, Coleman, undated (Box 80)
  - Conferences
    - Institute of Amorphous Studies -- opening ceremony, June 1985 (Box 80)
    - International conference on the Theory of the Structures of Non-Crystalline solids, June 1985 (Box 80)
    - SPIE -- Los Angeles, August 1985 (Box 80)
    - United States Advanced Battery Consortium, 1992 (Box 80)
  - Corporate Leadership Award, 2001 (Box 80)
  - Early Stan Ovshinsky
    - 1967 (Box 80)
    - Bump chart, undated (Box 80)
    - Hydrogen, 1964 (Box 80)
    - Labs, 1970-1997 (Box 80)
    - Labs -- Ovonic Memory Switch, undated (Box 80)
    - Life magazine, 1969 (Box 80)
      (with Iris Ovshinsky)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 80)
    - Ovonic Switching -- pipe cleaner model, undated (Box 80)
  - Electoluminsecent imaging, undated (Box 80)
  - England -- House of Parliament, 1977 (Box 80)
  - Equipment, undated (Box 80)
  - Equipment -- miscellaneous, undated (Box 80)
  - Events
    - Institute for Amorphous Studies, --, March 1984; June 1985 (Box 80)
      (TADIAS conference, Stan and Iris Ovshinsky anniversary)
    - Reception for Ray Tsu, April 1985 (Box 80)
  - Hydrogen research, undated (Box 80)
  - Institute for Amorphous Studies -- Lectures, 1986 (Box 80)
  - Japan
    - Fuji Film visit(?), 1971(?) (Box 80)
    - Lectures
      - Sponsored by Nihon Keizai Shinbun, January 31, 1978 (Box 80)
      - Nikkei Science, February 3, 1986 (Box 81)
    - Rightsholder, undated (Box 81)
  - Machines (Box 87)
    - 3 Megawatt machine (Box 87)
    - Big VEECO, undated (Box 81)
      (tool coating)
    - Continuous Deposition Plasma Processor, April 1987 (Box 81)
      (Herb's machine)
    - Microwave plasma deposition machine, undated (Box 81)
    - Molecular beam epitaxy system and ion beam implanter, undated (Box 81)
      (Includes class 60 clean room)
    - Plant 5A -- Transmission electron microscope, undated (Box 81)
    - Plant 11, undated (Box 81)
    - PV stitching machine, undated (Box 81)
    - SESI, 1982 (Box 81)
      (Sharp-ECD, Inc.. Japan)
    - Tandem II-A, undated (Box 81)